niresh.co 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy - Hackintosh Zone

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Hackintosh Zone collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [HackintoshZone.com](https://www.hackintoshzone.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Hackintosh Zone.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Hackintosh Zone may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. by registering or using this site without registering you are agreeing to follow [Terms of HackintoshZone.com](https://www.hackintoshzone.com/terms/), if you don't agrree with our terms stop using this site immidiately.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> or [New Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

**Google Analytics (Google)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

**AddThis (Addthis Inc.)**

AddThis is a service provided by Clearspring Technologies Inc., which displays a widget that allows interaction with social networks and external platforms as well as sharing the contents of this Website.

Depending on the configuration, this service can display widgets belonging to third parties such as the managers of social networks where interactions are shared. In this case, also the third parties that provide the widget will be informed of interactions and Usage Data on the pages where this service is installed.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy)

**Interaction with external social networks and platforms**

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.

The interaction and information obtained by this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.

If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

**Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook)**

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

**Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)**

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

These services allow this Website to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.

These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User.

**Access to the Facebook account (This Website)**

This service allows this Website to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

Permissions asked: Contact email.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

By registering or authenticating, Users allow this website to identify them and give them access to dedicated services.

Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services.

In this case, this Website will be able to access some Data, stored by these third party services, for registration or identification purposes.

**Twitter OAuth (Twitter)**

Twitter Oauth is a registration and authentication service provided by Twitter Inc. and is connected to the Twitter social network.

Personal Data collected: Various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://dev.twitter.com/terms/api-terms)

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Hackintosh Zone has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact via the [contact](https://www.hackintoshzone.com/contactus/) form found in this site

This document was last updated on February 14, 2015

  * _\- To improve customer service_

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * _\- To improve our Site_

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

  * _\- To send periodic emails_

We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
